A Guide to the Norfolk (Va.) Building Inspection Office Architectural Drawings and Plans, 1898-1980
Library of Virginia
- Storehouse - Permit Number: 58533, Address: Walnut St., 1948, Media: Blueprint, Diazo print; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1949-44 (Box 22, Folder 294)
  Drawn by: Truscon Steel Co., Youngstown, OH; Commissioned by: Imperial Tobacco Co.
- [Residence] - Permit Number: 60709, Address: 1115 W. Ocean View Ave., 1949, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1949-108 (Box 22, Folder 295)
  Drawn by: W. W. Powers; Contractor: George Gray; Commissioned by: George Gray
- Montecello Hotel Corp., Balcony for Air Conditioner and Hung Ceiling in Store - Permit Number: 60663, Address: 210 Granby St., 1948, Media: Bumwad; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1949-23 (Box 22, Folder 296)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Elliot and Co.; Commissioned by: Montecello Hotel Corp.
- Radio Store - Permit Number: 60165, Address: 4515 Colley Ave., 1949, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1949-64 (Box 22, Folder 297)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: J. M. Tebault
- Calvary Assembly of God [Church] - Permit Number: 66156, Address: 204 Delaware Ave., 1951, Media: Blueprints, Diazo prints; Sheets: 9; Tag Number: None (Box 23, Folder 298)
  Drawn by: Louis A. Oliver, A.I.A., Herbert L. Smith, III, A.I.A., Architects, 409 Yarmouth St., Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Calvary Assembly of God [Church]
- Eight Family Apartment Building for Highland Court Apartment Co. - Permit Number: 65832, Address: 1030-1032 W. 43rd St., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: None (Box 23, Folder 299)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Highland Court Apartment Co.
- [Five Family Apartment] - Permit Number: 65038, Address: 9329 Buckman Ave., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1951-68 (Box 23, Folder 300)
- Warehouse - Permit Number: 65955, Address: 1255 W. Ocean View Ave., 1951, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1951-77 (Box 23, Folder 301)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: S. D. Denny, Jr.; Notes: Large section torn and missing.
- Plans for Baxter Auto Service - Permit Number: 65391, Address: 2610 Church St., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1951-84 (Box 23, Folder 302)
  Drawn by: Thomas H. Boyle, Jr., 102 Chatham Circle, Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: J. W. Saunders, Jr.; Commissioned by: O. R. Baxter
- Proposed 28'-0" x 49'-4" Masonry and Stucco Service Station Building to be Located at Park Ave. and Broad Creek Rd. - Permit Number: 65098, Address: 1602 Broad Creek Rd., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1951-81 (Box 23, Folder 303)
  Drawn by: American Oil Company, Engineering Department, Richmond, Va.; Commissioned by: American Oil Co.
- Proposed Row Dwelling for Bishop C. M. Grace - Permit Number: 65614, Address: Princess Anne Rd. and Marathon Ave., 1951, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1951-73 (Box 23, Folder 304)
  Drawn by: Rudolph, Cooke, and Van Leeuwen, Inc., Architects, 355 Monticello Arcade Building, Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Bishop Grace Foundation
- U. S. Post Office, Customhouse Station - Permit Number: 64723, Address: 205 E. Main St., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1951-57 (Box 23, Folder 305)
  Drawn by: T. David Fitz-Gibbon, Architect, 932 Hoyster Building, Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: U. S. Post Office
- Office and Service Station for Cavalier Motor Co., Inc. - Permit Number: 65791, Address: 125 E. Olney Rd., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1951-72 (Box 23, Folder 306)
  Drawn by: Joseph B. Courtney, Architect, A.I.A., Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: R. D. Lambert
- [Standard Service Station with Lubridome] - Permit Number: 64420, Address: 126 E. Princess Anne Rd., 1951, Media: Blueprints, Blueline prints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1951-85 (Box 23, Folder 307)
  Drawn by: The Pure Oil Co., Engineering Dept., Chicago, Il.; Commissioned by: Colonial Oil Co.
- Campostella Elementary School for Negroes - Permit Number: None, Address: Cypress St. b/t Conoga and Melon Sts., 1952, Media: Blueprints, Diazo prints; Sheets: 29; Tag Number: None (Box 23, Folder 308)
  Drawn by: Alfred M. Lublin, Architect, 931 West 21st St., Norfolk, Va.; Reisner and Urbahn, Consultants, 645 Madison Ave, New York City
- [Shop, Warehouse, and Fabrication Plant for Hall-Hodges Co.] - Permit Number: 65341, Address: 1344 Ballentine Blvd., 1951, Media: Blueprints, Diazo print; Sheets: 15; Tag Number: 1951-71 (Box 23, Folder 309)
  Drawn by: Standard Iron and Steel Co., Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Hall-Hodges Co.
- Addition to Plant for Planters Chemical Corp. - Permit Number: 66297, Address: 3111 Broad Creek Rd. Rear, 1951, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1951-65 (Box 24, Folder 310)
  Drawn by: Norfolk Iron and Wire Works, Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Planters Chemical Corp.
- A Used Car Lot Office for Bratten-Roughton Motor Co. - Permit Number: 64543, Address: 4234 Granby St., 1951, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1951-59 (Box 24, Folder 311)
  Drawn by: A. Ray Pentecost, Jr., A.I.A., Architect, Nick Wright Building, Colonial Ave and 31st St., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Bratten-Roughton Motor Co.
- Building for Tidewater Motor Boat and Racing Association - Permit Number: 66333, Address: 2220 Kimball Ter., 1951, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1951-60 (Box 24, Folder 312)
  Drawn by: C. W. Hopkins, Jr.; Commissioned by: Tidewater Motor Boat and Racing Association
- Norfolk Harbor, Va, Harbor Lines, Eastern Branch of the Elizabeth River - Permit Number: None, Address: None, 1951, Media: Brownline print, paper; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1951-102 (Box 24, Folder 313)
  Drawn by: Corps of Engineers, U. S. Army, Office of the District Engineer, Norfolk, Va.; Notes: Outside of the roll has notation of "Davis Pier."
- Residence for Mr. and Mrs. J. Brody, Norfolk, Va. - Permit Number: 65202, 65203, 65204, Address: 7454, 7458, 7464 Millbrook Rd., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1951-15 (Box 24, Folder 314)
  Drawn by: E. Tucker Carlton, Architect, 1009 East Main St., Richmond, Va.; Commissioned by: Mr. and Mrs. J. Brody
- Store Building for Colonial Stores, Incorporated - Permit Number: 65718, Address: 1141 Campostella Rd., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: None (Box 24, Folder 315)
  Drawn by: William G. Bursnall, Architect, Colonial Stores Incorporated, 301-21 Dunmore St., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: P. W. Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Colonial Stores, Incorporated
- Warehouse, Bonney Motor Exp. - Permit Number: 64664, Address: 2315 E. Princess Anne Rd., 1951, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1951-69 (Box 24, Folder 316)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: R. D. Lambert; Commissioned by: Bonney Motor Exp.
- Reconditioning Building, 312 E. Freemason Street for United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local Union # 331 - Permit Number: 64276, Address: 312 E. Freemason St., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1951-86 (Box 24, Folder 317)
  Drawn by: T. David Fitz-Gibbon, Architect, 932 Royster Building, Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: E. E. Weddle and Co.; Commissioned by: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local Union # 331
- [Pentecostal Church] - Permit Number: 65304, Address: Wilson Rd. and Cypress St., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1951-87 (Box 24, Folder 318)
- A Three [Family] Apartment Building for Mrs. Louise Guthrie - Permit Number: 65560, Address: 1371 W. Ocean View Ave., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1951-67 (Box 24, Folder 319)
  Drawn by: Norfolk Builders; Contractor: Norfolk Builders; Commissioned by: Mrs. Louise Guthrie
- Six Unit, Two Story Apartment - Permit Number: 64792, 64793, 64794, Address: 1707-1711-1715 Kingston, 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1951-64 (Box 24, Folder 320)
  Drawn by: A. C. Sewell, B. A. Williams; Contractor: G. G. Sewell Construction Co.; Commissioned by: G. G. Sewell Construction Co.
- Alteration to Store Building for Mr. Alan Fleder - Permit Number: 65346, Address: 156-158 Church St., 1951, Media: Blueprints, Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1951-92 (Box 24, Folder 321)
  Drawn by: Alfred M. Lublin, A.I.A., Architect, Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Alan Fleder
- Storage Space Addition to 9302 Granby - Permit Number: 65792, Address: 9309 Granby St., 1951, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1951-80 (Box 24, Folder 322)
  Drawn by: E. D. Denny; Commissioned by: P. J. Boogades
- [Addition] - Permit Number: 65133, Address: 817 Freemont St., 1951, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1951-95 (Box 24, Folder 323)
  Drawn by: Robert L. Dixon; Commissioned by: Sara B. Patterson
- The Abbots Hardware Store, Cinder Block Addition, 24' 0" x 30' 0", for Mr. Louis Friedman - Permit Number: 65796, Address: 1415 Colley Ave., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1951-98 (Box 24, Folder 324)
  Drawn by: J. B. Wooding; Commissioned by: Louis Friedman
- [Cooling Tower for Norfolk Newspapers] - Permit Number: 66417, Address: 150 W. Brambleton Ave., 1951, Media: Blueprint, Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1951-55 (Box 24, Folder 325)
  Drawn by: Water Cooling Equipment, St. Louis, Mo.; Commissioned by: Norfolk Newspapers
- Proposed Addition to Hampton Roads Tractor and Equipment Co. - Permit Number: 64622, Address: 3814 Killam Ave., 1951, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1951-91 (Box 24, Folder 326)
  Drawn by: L. Birsch, Jr.; Commissioned by: Hampton Roads Tractor and Equipment Co.
- Used Car Department, Alterations and Additions to Building 6, Colonial Chevrolet - Permit Number: 66324, Address: 138-140 W. Olney Rd., 1951, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1951-56 (Box 24, Folder 327)
  Drawn by: Bernard B. Spigel, Architect, Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Colonial Chevrolet
- Office and Warehouse Building, 21st St. and Core Ave., Norfolk, Va., Orkin Exterminating Co. - Permit Number: 66041, 66206, Address: 839 W 21st St., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: None (Box 24, Folder 328)
  Drawn by: Wilfred L. Keel, A.I.A., Architect, Atlanta, Ga.; Commissioned by: Orkin Exterminating Co.
- [Alteration] - Permit Number: 64415, Address: 740 Granby St., 1951, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: None (Box 24, Folder 329)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Atlanta Equipment
- Proposed Store Front for Curtis Marine Co., Inc. - Permit Number: 64486, Address: 548-556 Front St., 1951, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1951-61 (Box 24, Folder 330)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Curtis Marine Co., Inc.
- Esso Standard Oil Co., Addition to Barrel Filling Building - Permit Number: 65730, Address: Hampton Blvd., 1951, Media: Blueprint, Diazo print; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1951-76 (Box 24, Folder 331)
  Drawn by: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc., Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Standard Oil Co.
- Addition for the Seay Motor Co. - Permit Number: 65383, Address: 2314 Colonial Ave., 1951, Media: Blueprint, Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1952-27 (Box 24, Folder 332)
  Drawn by: Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co., Distributing Branches, Construction Dept., Grant Building, Pittsburgh, Pa.; Commissioned by: Seay Motor Co.
- Alterations and Additions for Batchelder and Collins - Permit Number: 65612, Address: 2301 Granby St., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1951-62 (Box 24, Folder 333)
  Drawn by: Rudolph, Cooke, and Van Leeuwen, Inc., Architects, 355 Monticello Arcade Building, Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Batchelder and Collins
- Plan for a Building for the Lorraine Press - Permit Number: None, Address: Church St., 1951, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1951-75 (Box 24, Folder 334)
  Drawn by: Jack Robinson, West Ocean View Ave., Norfolk, Va., Contractor and Builder; Contractor: Jack Robinson; Commissioned by: The Lorraine Press, Samuel Baras, Prop.
- Carrolton Oaks School - Permit Number: 66391, Address: Granby St., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1951-63 (Box 24, Folder 335)
- Storage Addition - Permit Number: 66269, Address: 507 Front St., 1951, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1951-58 (Box 24, Folder 336)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Norfolk Marine Co.
- Furnace Room, 228 E. Indian River Rd. - Permit Number: 65186, Address: 228 E. Indian River Rd., 1951, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1951-66 (Box 24, Folder 337)
  Drawn by: C. E. Miles; Commissioned by: C. E. Miles
- Multi-Dwelling for Vernon Hayman - Permit Number: 65151, Address: 217 W/ Sewells Point Rd., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1952-17 (Box 25, Folder 338)
  Drawn by: T. Nelson Worley, Designer; Commissioned by: H. V. Hayman
- Norfolk Motors Co., Inc., Lubrication Department - Permit Number: 66261, Address: 1400 Monticello Ave. Rear, 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1952-22 (Box 25, Folder 339)
  Drawn by: Bernard B. Spigel, Architect, 200 Dickson Building, Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Norfolk Motors Co., Inc.
- Plans of a Factory Building for Sutton Manufacturing Corporation - Permit Number: 65036, Address: 116-122 W. Wilson Ave., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1952-29 (Box 25, Folder 340)
  Drawn by: John A. Simpson, Architect; Commissioned by: Sutton Manufacturing Corp.
- [Apartments] - Permit Number: 66387, Address: Little Bay Ave., 1951, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1952-35 (Box 25, Folder 341)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: George Jensen
- Bayfront Hotel - Permit Number: 65433, Address: 424 E. Ocean View Ave., 1951, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1951-30 (Box 25, Folder 342)
  Drawn by: Alfred M. Lublin, A.I.A., Architect, Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Bayfront Corporation
- Proposed Retarder Tower and Shop Building, Lamberts Point, Norfolk, Va. - Permit Number: 66298, Address: Lamberts Point, 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 9; Tag Number: 1952-25 (Box 25, Folder 343)
  Drawn by: Norfolk and Western Railway Co., Norfolk Terminal Division; Commissioned by: Norfolk and Western Railway Co.
- Addition # 1 to Hoffman Cigar Co. - Permit Number: 66392, Address: 237 W. 24th St., 1951, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1952-26 (Box 25, Folder 344)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: C. B. Duke and Son; Commissioned by: Hoffman Cigar Co.
- Pipe Storage Shed for Noland Company - Permit Number: 53395, Address: 2406 Church St., 1951, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1952-34 (Box 25, Folder 345)
  Drawn by: Rudolph, Cooke, and Van Leeuwen, Inc., Architects, 355 Monticello Arcade Building, Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Noland Company
- Christ Methodist Church - Permit Number: 65715, Address: 1601 Bay View Blvd., 1951, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1952-70 (Box 25, Folder 346)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Christ Methodist Church
- Remodeling of Storage Building of Norfolk Newspapers, Inc. - Permit Number: 64965, Address: 747 National Ln., 1951, Media: Negative photostat; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1952-18 (Box 25, Folder 347)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: R. R. Richardson and Sons; Commissioned by: Norfolk Newspaper, Inc.
- 4 Family Apartment - Permit Number: 65206, Address: 1635 Kingston Ave., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1952-32 (Box 25, Folder 348)
  Drawn by: Thomas H. Boyle, Jr., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: A. C. Mock; Commissioned by: H. C. Hopkins
- Alterations, First Baptist Church - Permit Number: 65268, Address: 400 Westover Ave., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1952-31 (Box 25, Folder 349)
  Drawn by: Rudolph, Cooke, and Van Leeuwen, Inc., Architects, 355 Monticello Arcade Building, Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: Gregory Construction Co.; Commissioned by: First Baptist Church
- Addition to Building for American Tobacco Co. - Permit Number: 66115, Address: 1235 Courtney St., 1951, Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1952-20 (Box 25, Folder 350)
  Drawn by: Rudolph, Cooke, and Van Leeuwen, Inc., Architects, 355 Monticello Arcade Building, Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: American Tobacco Co.
- Store Building for L and M Realty Corporation - Permit Number: 64342, Address: 301 W. 21st St., 1952, Media: Blueprints, Diazo prints; Sheets: 22; Tag Number: None (Box 25, Folder 351)
  Drawn by: Bernard B. Spigel, Architect; Contractor: E. E. Weddle and Co.; Commissioned by: L and M Realty Corp.
- Alterations and Addition to Berkley Pentecostal Holiness Church - Permit Number: 65785, Address: Chestnut St., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: None (Box 25, Folder 352)
  Drawn by: Alex. O. Ferebee, Architect; Commissioned by: Berkley Pentecostal Holiness Church
- Fellowship House for Second Congregational Christian Church - Permit Number: None, Address: Restmere and Sewells Point Rds., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: None (Box 25, Folder 353)
  Drawn by: Rudolph, Cooke, and Van Leeuwen, Inc., Architects, 355 Monticello Arcade Building, Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Second Congregational Christian Church
- [Norfolk Municipal Airport Grounds and Buildings] - Permit Number: None, Address: N/A, ca. 1939, Media: Linen and ink, bumwad, and Diazo prints; Sheets: 71; Tag Number: 1952-49 (Box 26, Folder 354)
  Drawn by: Various; Commissioned by: N/A; Notes: Group consists of sketches, tracings, linen, and Diazo prints for the Norfolk Municipal Airport grounds and buildings.
- Park Avenue Baptist Church - Permit Number: 61056, Address: 1906 Pershing Ave., 1949, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1949-91 (Box 26, Folder 355)
  Drawn by: Rudolph, Cooke, and Van Leeuwen, Inc., Architects, 355 Monticello Arcade Building, Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: R. R. Richardson; Commissioned by: Park Avenue Baptist Church
- Alterations and Repair to Venice Restaurant - Permit Number: 59215, Address: 4016 Granby St., 1949, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1949-121 (Box 26, Folder 356)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: C. Wooton; Commissioned by: Alban Loeircio; Notes: See also Permit # 59178 (January 1949).
- [Apartment] - Permit Number: 60423, Address: 318-320 W. 30th St., 1949, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1949-100 (Box 26, Folder 357)
  Drawn by: Clarence Wooton; Contractor: Cullifer Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Mrs. Woodfin G. Willis
- 1 1/2 Story [Residence] - Permit Number: 55228, Address: 424 N. Shore Rd., 1947, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1952-42 (Box 26, Folder 358)
  Drawn by: Harry Adelman, Architect, 7400 Granby St., Norfolk; Contractor: Albert Solomon, Builder; Commissioned by: Hyman Teitler
- Apartment Building for Mr. and Mrs. Zeke Newburg - Permit Number: 64904, Address: 1512 Hampton Blvd., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1951-41 (Box 26, Folder 359)
  Drawn by: Charles P. Leavitt & Associates, Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Mr. and Mrs. Zeke Newburg
- Plans of a Warehouse for C. E. Thurston, Jr. - Permit Number: 64998, Address: 407 E. Water St., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1951-48 (Box 26, Folder 360)
  Drawn by: John A. Simpson, Architect; Contractor: James A. Carney; Commissioned by: C. E. Thurston; Notes: Plans for replacement of a building destroyed by fire.
- Building for the Builders and Contractors Exchange - Permit Number: 68492, Address: 210 E. 21st St., 1952, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1952-17 (Box 26, Folder 361)
  Drawn by: Rudolph, Cooke, and Van Leeuwen, Inc., Architects, 355 Monticello Arcade Building, Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: W. A. Hall and Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Builders and Contractors Exchange, Inc.
- 3 Bay Service Station- Types C49 - Permit Number: 64379, Address: 8031 Hampton Blvd., 1951, Media: Blueprints, Diazo print; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1951-4 (Box 26, Folder 362)
  Drawn by: Sun Oil Company, Engineering Dept., Marketing Division, 1600 Walnut St., Philadelphia, Pa.; Commissioned by: Taylor Oil Co.
- Store Remodeling for James Albano - Permit Number: 59537, Address: 85 W. Ocean View Ave., 1949, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1949-133 (Box 26, Folder 363)
  Drawn by: Lublin, McGaughy and Associates, Architects and Engineers, Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: James A. Albano
- Residence - Permit Number: 68974, Address: 1500 Pratt St., 1952, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1952-2 (Box 26, Folder 364)
  Drawn by: Paul D. Woodward, A.I.A., Architect, 716 Boush St., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: Master Bros.; Commissioned by: Webb Realty Co.
- Four Family Apartment, Norfolk Academy - Permit Number: 66569, Address: 201 N. Shore Rd., 1951, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1952-9 (Box 26, Folder 365)
  Drawn by: Joseph B. Courtney, Architect, A.I.A., Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: Norfolk Academy
- Rebuilding Empire Machinery and Supply Corp., Damaged by Fire - Permit Number: 64362, Address: 409-417 Water St., 1951, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 20; Tag Number: 1952-7 (Box 27, Folder 366)
  Drawn by:; Contractor: V. T. Myers; Commissioned by: Empire Machinery
- Plans for a Store Building for Mr. and Mrs. I. M. Baker, Jr. - Permit Number: 61128, Address: 114-116 W. Princess Anne Rd., 1949, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1949-90 (Box 27, Folder 367)
  Drawn by: John A. Simpson, Architect; Contractor: I. M. Baker, Jr.; Commissioned by: Mr. and Mrs. I. M. Baker, Jr.
- Sewell's Point Branch, Southern Bank of Norfolk - Permit Number: 64376, Address: 143 E. Sewells Point Rd., 1950, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1951-39 (Box 27, Folder 368)
  Drawn by: Bernard B. Spigel, A.I.A., Architect; Contractor: R. S. De Loatch Const.; Commissioned by: Southern Bank of Norfolk
- Martin Apartment for The George Martin Beach Corp. - Permit Number: 59428, Address: 7328, 7330, 7332 Hampton Blvd., 1949, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1949-105 (Box 27, Folder 369)
  Drawn by: John A. Simpson, Architect, 408 McKevitt Building, Norfolk, Va.; John M. Baldwin, Civil Engineer, Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: George E. Gray; Commissioned by: George Martin Beach Corp.
- Low Rent Housing Project, VA 6-7, Norfolk Redevelopment and Housing Authority - Permit Number: 65418, Address: Ballentine Blvd., 1951, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 23; Tag Number: 1951-38 (Box 27, Folder 370)
  Drawn by: Bernard B. Spigel, A.I.A., Dickson Building, Norfolk, Va.; Churchill-Fulmer Associates, 79 West 44th St., NY, Ny.; Contractor: Bush Construction Company, Inc.; Commissioned by: Norfolk Redevelopment and Housing Authority
- Alterations for First Calvary Baptist Church, Rev. C. E. Griffin, Pastor - Permit Number: 59315, Address: Wide and Henry Sts., 1949, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1949-126 (Box 27, Folder 371)
  Drawn by: Hilyard R. Robinson, Architect, Washington, DC; Commissioned by: First Calvary Baptist Church
- Tankar Stations Office and Storehouse - Permit Number: 59631, Address: 1083 W. 37th St., 1949, Media: Blueprints, Diazo print; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1949-92 (Box 27, Folder 372)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Tankar Stations Office and Storehouse
- Two Service Bay Servicenter, Stucco and Concrete Block, 30' Deep Lube Pit - Permit Number: 67578, Address: 2911 Lafayette Blvd., 1952, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 11; Tag Number: 1952-60 (Box 27, Folder 373)
  Drawn by: Esso Standard Oil Company, Marketing Department, Construction and Maintenance, 15 W. 51st St., New York, Ny.; Contractor: R. A. Ladd, III, Construction; Commissioned by: Esso Standard Oil Company
- Building for Mr. A. D. Harrell - Permit Number: 59843, Address: 609 Manteo St., 1949, Media: Blueprint, Diazo print; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1949-144 (Box 27, Folder 374)
  Drawn by: S. S. Lancaster, Royster Co.; Commissioned by: A. D. Harrell
- Addition to Plant - Permit Number: 61164, Address: 3111 Broad Creek Rd., 1950, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1949-104 (Box 27, Folder 375)